terrysfabrics.co.uk 2019-09-10

# Privacy Policy / Statement

## Cookies

**Visiting Terrys Fabrics websites with your browser settings adjusted to accept cookies tells us that you want to use Terrys Fabrics products and services and that you consent to our use of cookies and other technologies to provide them to you as described in this notice and in privacy notice**. 

Please see our online guide for more information about cookies. You may wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a new cookie or you may wish to disable cookies altogether, this guide will help you to modify the settings in your browser.  
We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors of this site, which can include using a "cookie" that is stored on your browser. 

Please note that we have the ability to retain any data that you provide on this website using VeCapture by Ve Interactive, even if you do not complete your registration/transaction by clicking submit/next. Such contact details and data may be used to contact you to enquire why you did not complete your registration/transaction and improve our online operations.

Upon payment of a fee and by written request, you are entitled to a copy of the personal data held about you by us, as provided for under the Data Protection Act.

You also have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your information.

We reserve the right to amend our privacy policy/statement, and any amendment will be clearly published on our website.

## Privacy Policy/Statement 

We are Terry’s Textiles Limited. You can contact us by telephone, or by email by clicking here to contact us

We store personal information about you to provide our products and services to you and to promote our products and services to you. 

We do this because it is necessary for us to do so to run our business. 

The personal information we store is your name, postal address, email address, telephone and fax numbers. We keep this information for as long as we believe we need to in order to promote our products and services to you and in order to fulfil our contractual promises and guarantees to you. 

We do not store credit card details. Our shopping platform Shopify does have options to store credit card information, but we do not have access to your credit card details, as these are stored by our partner Shopify.

Other than explained below, we will keep your personal information private and confidential. We will also keep your personal information secure and share it securely.

We share your personal information with our business partners which include (but are not limited to) Shopify, Ekomi, Mailchimp, Loyalty Lion and our nominated carriers. Shopify provide our e-commerce platform. Ekomi collect feedback from customers so that we can improve our service. Mailchimp provide our marketing and email services. Loyalty Lion manage our loyalty programme. Our carriers deliver our products to our customers.

Apart from this we do not normally share your personal information with anyone else

If you object to us handling your personal information in the way we have explained you can ask us free of charge to stop by [clicking here](https://help.terrysfabrics.co.uk/support/tickets/new). 

We will comply with any reasonable request by you to erase or correct your personal information. We will provide a copy of you personal information to you on your request. To make any of these requests please click here. We may need to verify your identity before acting on your request but we will not charge you anything for exercising your rights.

You can see specific details of our cookies policy and the cookies we use on terrysfabrics.co.uk by clicking here.

## Klarna

In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass certain aspects of your personal information to Klarna, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you.

General information on Klarna can be found [here](https://www.klarna.com/uk/ "Klarna General"). Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in [Klarna’s privacy policy](http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy "Klarna Privacy Policy").
